Nathan Zura and a man who needs no
introduction, but he'll get one anyway.
The greatest linebacker, coach, walking
God's green earth, friend of the show,
best friend of the show, really. I think
it's safe to say I think we can say
that. Santa Clara alum, obviously went
through a lot of ups and downs over the
the last few days, the great Jason
Tarver. Tarfs, how are you?
>> I'm great. Thanks for the great
introduction. Again, you're you're
really good at changing it up every
time.
>> Well, you got to keep it fresh. We got
to keep it fresh. You know, you got so
many accolades. We got to keep it fresh
and mix in certain things here or there.
All right, let's talk tournament real f
at first. Let's start it off. Santa
Clara Cinderella story. Everybody in the
world rooting for them except Dr. Jay in
there because of his bracket. The what
an outrageous reason to root against the
Cinderella story.
>> They hit the three. I'm calling you. I
was right there. I was blowing up your
phone. No answer. You were too dialed.
>> Go up three. What do you think is going
to happen? Like you thought they were
going to win, right?
>> Oh man. Well, I thought they were going
to get that timeout. That would have
been awesome at But
>> should have gotten the timeout. Coach,
as soon as it's through, right? The
guy's here. Timeout. reminded me of the
of the bank shot by Gonzaga against
UCLA, which broke my heart, too, cuz I
went there as well. But
>> yes,
>> that's why they call it March Madness.
>> That's why they call it the madness. Did
you have the same feeling that I did
that once the guy from Kentucky hit the
crazy shot that in overtime it was that
was it
>> as a coach or you can't I don't go
there. I just give me whatever's time on
the clock and let's go. That's my gut.
So, that's what I was hoping for and
hoping for. I mean, we hadn't been in
for 30 years. Crazy.
>> I know. Crazy. It would have been a It
would have been awesome. Santa Clara,
obviously Steve Nash back in the day
beat Arizona was a 15 seed,
>> which was, you know, my elite I do have
some Arizona allegiance. That made me
sad. The fact that it made you happy
though eases the pain a little bit.
>> It did. I was a senior in high school,
but then I got to um then I got to go
there when we had that run with with
Steve Nash. That was a lot of fun.
>> Which is crazy.
>> Yeah.
>> And the funny thing is and not funny
thing, but the just the changing college
landscape now. There's no way Steve Nash
finishes his career at Santa Clara
today.
>> Yeah. Probably not. I mean, everybody
moves
>> big money. Yeah, he'd be he'd be playing
somewhere. You probably play at Duke for
big big money. All right, let's talk a
little bit about this offseason, this
football team, you know, defensively for
you coming in. And we got to meet We had
uh Rudy in here. That was last week,
right, Gay?
>> And he did 25 minutes. He's awesome. I
mean, you told me I was going to love
him. I I I'm not so sure you guys aren't
like part of the same person. There's a
lot of similarities in your guys'
personality and energy and approach and
all of that, but uh we really liked
them. What's it been like? you know, for
you coming in. He's come in. You guys
are really the same coaching staff.
You've added some more people. We got a
much bigger staff now. But coming in
with with Rudy.
>> Yeah, we're about half and half. I've
been waiting to Rudy and Coach Rudy and
I have been waiting to coach together,
you know, for a while since we met. And
lot of great coaches in common.
>> Y
>> uh Jeff Albert, Robert Saw, everybody.
And uh you know, energy all the time.
Love it. Smart. Great with it. you know,
great with just caring about people and
and checking on you and and same dude
every day. So, it's going to be a lot of
fun.
>> Heart, mind, fist. That's what he g
that's what he gave us, the heart, mind,
fist. That's one of the big things
there. We're going to be violent
football team, which I always love the
sound of that. And then you mentioned
how he relates so well to his players.
The newest addition into your room, uh,
Quincy Williams. I got a chance to talk
with him. Rudy talked about him kind not
in his introductory press conference
before he was even a Cleveland Brown,
believe it or not.
It's wild when you those bonds matter so
much in this league and to bring a guy
in like Quincy who no shortage of energy
there either.
>> No, not at all. And you know, Rudy and
Quincy worked together two different
stops
>> and he's played his best ball with him
uh in same forms of scheme as we run and
all we asked him was be the same guy
every day. Bring the energy, right?
Carson likes to play catch before
practice. Let's get out there, play
catch. Let's let's get everybody going
because he will be the most veteran in
our linebacker room this year and and
we're excited about him because he can
run. He sheds blocks well. He makes
explosion plays that we need in our
defense and he's done that. So, need him
to be the same every day, which I think
he will and and he'll fit in our group
really good and help help us with some
of the guys that haven't seen the field
yet that are raring to go.
>> Yeah. I mean, back in 2023, he was a
first team allpro. First team AllPro.
That is the highest honor really you can
get in the game. Um
>> yeah, he said he wants to do it again. I
said, "Well, you got to beat Carson to
the ball and everybody else and Miles,
so let's go beat him to the ball. That'd
be great."
>> That's right. I mean, four last five
seasons over 100 tackles. You mentioned
the first team all pro. That's exactly
what he said. He said, "I want to be
first team all pro again." That is his
personal uh goal playing there next to
Carson. And for you, that will
linebacker spot has been so productive,
but it's been a bit of a revolving door.
Unfortunately, Jeremiah gets hurt two
years ago. Deb played so well last year
and is rewarded with a big contract goes
to the Chicago Bears, which we're sad to
see him go. And now here comes Quincy
Williams. So really the the week one
starter there or the guy you were
counting on to be a big productive part
of the defense three years in a row.
It's going to be three different guys.
You've always been able to roll with the
punches in your room, you know, how do
you get him up to speed and and working
with Carson in that, you know, with our
base defense is two linebackers.
>> Yeah. And and well, I'll say this. I
mean, our goal is to get 11 people on
defense to stop the offense no matter
what it takes. And the better we do
that, the more everybody gets rewarded.
So really proud for Dev and everybody
and just excited for for Q to get in
here. But same thing, he's been in this
defense. He's been in pieces with it
with Rudy. So there's a nice piece that
he's heard some of the words and so his
transition should be quick. And that'll
be, you know, it's like anything. It's a
different language wherever you go in,
but we're keeping a lot the same. Keep
it easy. So that way, you know, he'll be
able to come in and get going and we
need him to right away.
>> Yeah. For you, what's the challenge
where you're going to have a linebacker
room as it sits right now,
>> Carson's really the only guy that played
for you last year.
>> You know, Mahmood is is now in
Tennessee. Dev is, as you talked about
there, is in Chicago. Quincy has
experience, but guys, Pooky Watson was
out with an injury. Winston Reed was out
with an injury. Een Mascarinas Arnold
played very limited defensive snaps.
Could there be a rookie out of that
room? Yes. Could there be a veteran?
Yes, but it's not going to be guys who
have been here. So, how do you as a as
the teacher and as the leader of that
room, how do you get these guys? A lot
of those guys were in the classroom,
Watson and Reed, but how do you get
these guys up to speed and how do you
get everybody jelling and rowing in the
same direction?
>> Well, the good part was is with with
Nate and with Winston, they were in the
room the whole year when they were on IR
and they were actually they were just
studying the scheme and they were they
were they knew the scheme as good as
anybody. I mean, they would they would
get after people they didn't know the
answers. So that's good. Both those two
are hydract
squad at the end of last year. They all
like contact. They're all they're all
doing the drills needed to help their
movement, which when they got here, the
all four of them have improved already.
So now, just like what happened at the
end of last year with Jordan Hicks
retiring, somebody's going to get a turn
as the as the third, fourth, fifth guy,
and it's going to be competition in
camp. Same thing we said last year, like
let's see who wins. I'm excited for all
four of those guys to see them be who
they can be with an opportunity to play
the reps. But I like where they've gone
mentally. That gives them the chance.
That's the same thing that Jeremiah did
in offseasons. That's the same thing
obviously Jordan Hicks as smart as he
did, Cion, Anthony Walker, I mean all
the way back, those guys gave themselves
a chance in the offseason by their
mental and physical preparation. And
these these young guys are doing that
and we need them to. and that's their
job. Next thing is is every year is its
own deal. We've seen this before.
Nothing matters. Nothing matters. It's
about going 1 and0 every week. And when
we start, whatever date it is in a few
weeks,
>> we're going and that's what we do.
>> And whoever's in that room, that's our
job to run, shed, and tackle the guy
with the ball. And that's just how it
works.
>> Yeah. When you look at it, Carson
obviously defensive rookie of the year,
the Mike linebacker, Quincy in that will
spot. You're going to be looking for
that that Sam, that third guy that's
typically been a bigger guy, more
physical guy. Mammud's been in that role
for us at times. You know, how do you
look at at that competition? You said
it's going to be competition. You like
to get guys in a lot of different spots
because you're going to need people at
different spots. Somebody goes down,
somebody has to slide over, be the mic
or whatever how that goes. But how do
you kind of look at that competition for
that that we'll call just that Sam spot?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I'm with you. I The first
thing with with young players is you you
want to give them a home. You want to
give them a home position. Yeah.
>> But all of these guys that have been in
know now that hey, there's three
linebacker spots. We just got
linebackers. We don't necessarily have a
name on them, but whoever ends up
getting the reps in there and wins is
going to play. And maybe it's a rotation
like we've done in the past. We've used
Jerome Baker and Mahmood to to in
different spots. We've used Devin his
first year in different spots. And then
Devin took over a little bit more last
year. Great. You earn it, right? Andrew
Luck said, "Football's the ultimate
meritocracy." What's that mean? You get
what you earn. The better you play, the
more you get to play. Yep.
>> And that's just what it is. And we'll
we'll roll them in and all the reps in
the offseason, all the reps in in in
training camp are going to be big for
these guys to see if they can who is
going to own it and or who's going to
get into the rotation.
>> What made Carson so special last year?
how quick he can see things and and make
adjustments and not make anything too
big and just when he sees things or he
he can self-correct as fast as anybody
I've ever seen in and any field, not
just football. He's amazing. He does it
within plays sometimes.
>> Yeah.
>> Um he jumped when a quarterback pump
fake once early in the year. He came off
the sideline says, "Coach JT, I'm not
going to do that again." And then you
saw him against Josh Allen later. Just
run right at him. You saw him against
Green Bay. Just run right Jordan Love
one that was nuts.
>> That's like it's just he he can lock in
and and do it at real live fast speed
and that is an elite trait.
>> What do you hope to see from him?
Because when you when you play that well
there come great expectations and quite
frankly as we just went through your
room we need him to be really darn good
again. What's the kind of year one to
year two what you hope would be a leap?
Where can he you know continue to
improve?
>> Good. We've talked about some of this,
but Cars can listen right now and do it.
Uh, a little there's there's some things
as he cleans up his feet that he can get
uh back and set up a little bit quicker.
And he's really good at it, don't get me
wrong, but we can even get more out of
some breaking on the ball. I mean, they
went through a phase, I said it on here,
where they didn't even throw the ball
near him for a bunch of games. And if
that continues, we're gonna be a pretty
good defense again. So, there's some
things we can clean up with his
breaking. um there's some things that we
can do more with them that we haven't
done as much, which is pass rush games
and blitzing and things like that. So,
we'll continue to work on on that kind
of movement. We go down with the Dline
and we compete against them and and and
you know, the the some of the other
coaches go crazy. I'm more excited about
when the guys win, but let's say we've
just get Carson's gotten better and
better at some of the pass rush things.
So, keeping him going on that
progression and then things around the
ball. We see if we can get some more
force fumbles, things like that as he
because he finishes at the pile so well
and it'll happen. It's coming because
he's thinking about it, he's conscious
about it and so the more he continues to
finish around the pile because
>> how you force takeaways as we know is a
lot of times the second, third, fourth,
fifth man into a pile or somebody
somebody's struggling,
>> he's usually the first guy in the pile.
>> So that's exactly so maybe when he gets
somebody else in there for maybe Q.
Let's go Q. Get Q Q there first. We're
good.
>> Yeah, absolutely. I mean, you think
about it. You had it 156 tackles, 11
tackles for a loss. He had the two
interceptions, three passes defense, no
force fumbles to your point right there,
nine quarterback hits on the season, two
and a half sacks, and you know this, I
pretty sure he had at least two, maybe
three, where he got a sack that was
taken away on a penalty. Yeah. Had
anything to do with that.
>> Yeah, a couple penalty ones. But his his
pass rush win percentage was good, and
we got to keep getting that better and
better. get it better and better. All
right, we talk about your room and it
does seem like this is, you know, we've
done a good job identifying some of
these guys in the draft or as undrafted
free agents who have come in, played
well under your toutelage at the
combine. One of the treats for me as I
throw the TV on and all of a sudden
there's you leading the linebacker
drills. I did you hear what they said
about you? They were putting you over
big. It was I think Charles Davis and
Jeremiah and Eisen putting you over
huge. They're like, "Oh, Jason Tarver,
all the energy. Love him. Great coach,
great teacher, all this." I'm like,
"That's our guy. How fun was that for
you to be out there at the combine and
and you know, listen, when you're
looking at a room that maybe could use
another piece or so to be able to get
your eye, see them move, feel them,
learn a little bit about their
personality. How valuable was that?
>> I love doing the drills at the combine.
Just like you said, the energy, all
that's awesome, but it the best part is
to meet all the all the young men, all
the all the guys all at the same time.
See how they compete, get to know them,
you know, give them a coaching point,
see if they can put it into effect,
which was awesome.
>> How do you get to do that?
How? Well, you sign up. You you sign up.
Your organization gets so many spots.
So, um, shout out to Megan. Megan puts
me on the list every year because I said
as soon as I got back, I want to do it
every year. And, uh, I love that
opportunity.
>> They keep picking you.
>> Yeah.
>> That was like you, B. Lynch.
>> We had a bunch of coaches that were out
there.
>> That was awesome. Coach Lynch is doing
it now, too, which is good. He's he's
great.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, but I just love the ability to see
them all at once. I love the ability to
see them all at once and to hopefully
give them something for their careers
because you can't have them all, you
know, but you don't know when we're
going to cross paths. Might be somebody
now that I had that I worked with down
there remembers me and then we're able
to work together or we're able to,
>> you know, get them in here because of
that interaction. You never know.
>> I just think it's cool and you have such
a zest for teaching and such an aptitude
for it that you it just seems like you
were having the time of your life out
there.
>> Yeah, it's awesome. It's a lot of fun.
Rudy and I actually did those drills
together a few years back. So, and you
get to know the other coaches and you
get to see all all of the guys, all the
kids, all the scouts who interact with
the kids are down there. So, it's just
it's just awesome experience
>> with the linebackers. Are there drills
that you is it just like here these are
the drills and they're set or do you get
an opportunity to to mold them or
massage those drills?
>> Good question. The one that I do is one
we've changed. It used to be a 45 degree
angle drill, but linebackers don't do
that as much anymore where they're just
going up the hash.
>> So, the one we do, the shuffle, run,
change direction, spin back. That's one
we added a few years ago because
everybody wants to see
>> a linebacker do those movements because
that happens all the time. You run, you
got to turn it back into a shuffle, then
you got to break somewhere to make a
tackle, then you got to turn and get
out. And so, and we modified it a little
bit over the years. Now, they don't want
to change too much, but if it's a drill
like that that is a movement that the
other ones don't show, that's when some
of them change. But a lot of them are,
it's said in an order to see the players
do what they need by position and
they're pretty well thought out and
they're, you know, there's a committee
of GMs and scouts that do it.
>> That's okay. That's
>> I don't know if you could try to put a
few things in there that you know
>> Justin runs it. Justin runs it. He's a
scout for the Niners. He runs it and we
work together well. So, um, it's a it's
a good process, but it it does you have
to talk about it before you can change
it. We've added one of the drills we
come up with, the linebackers come off
the bags. We've added a scoop after the
finish line just because everybody wants
to see the guys see how they scoop and
how they bend down to get the ball.
Yeah. And those things. So, we added
that a few years ago, too. So, there is
there are some changes, but the the
overall core is built because each drill
does a different movement that everybody
wants to see.
How much for you personally,
how much draft stuff do you do before
the combine or is that something that
you do after the combine? So when you go
to the combine, you're doing these
drills, are you like total blank slate?
You're like, "Oh, I like the way this
guy moves." But you hadn't watched them
yet or had you watched them and had some
preconceived notions? Well, some of the
guys when you have the formal interviews
like we had with Arll, you got to get
the video ready and study them a little
bit more because you have a formal
interview with whoever's in the room,
your head coach, your general manager,
scouts, whoever's in the room. All teams
do that differently.
>> So, there's you got to prepare that one.
You want to see them a little bit more
because you want to ask specific
questions. So, we did that and Arll did
really well, which is awesome.
>> And but then some of the others you
don't have time
>> to see everybody. Yeah. So, like you
said when you started the question, this
is this is always the deal. Everybody
has bias no matter what it is. And all
biases are different, right? We all have
it. Y
>> we all have our own thoughts and that's
great. Different is not bad. It's just
different. We say that all the time.
That's what everybody loves about being
in the room because that's what we do.
>> And so, I really do just watch and
listen and try to learn them as a human
and how they move. But then I'm gonna go
back and even in the interview process,
my sheet where I ask them questions, I
say, "Write down your your strengths and
things you need to work on." And when I
watch the video, I watch it with what I
talk to them about because I want to see
if they're telling the truth. Yeah. And
>> um I don't want to be biased one way or
the other.
>> Actually, uh this strength is not a
strength. Yeah.
>> Right. Yeah. Like are you telling the
truth or not? I want to know. So they
like, "Tell me what you're good at. Tell
me what you need to work on." I'm good
with that. But so that's the way I go
about it. All I do is watch, see if I
can help them have the best day they can
because I want everybody to play as long
as they can in the league. That's our
job as a coach is Yeah. I want everybody
everybody to have success. That's why we
do what we do. But
>> and then I go back and watch it. I was
actually just inputting some of the the
writeups right before we started talking
today. That's what I was working on. So
>> then we go back and we see them all and
and then compare and contrast and we'll
go back and watch like if I think I miss
something I'll go watch combine again in
addition to plays or I'll watch their
pro day if they didn't whatever didn't
run the 40 or didn't do
>> the movement because it needed movement
like uh I know I'm long but this is a
good one like Carson last year he had a
hamstring so he really couldn't run so I
I was with him on the field at the
combine of course you know the UA
background and I'm like why aren't you
doing something? What's going on? Yeah.
and uh in my not really mean but direct
questioning way and uh I'm like I can't
wait to watch you move. Do you need
anything? You know, and then then he got
good enough to do the movement drills
and then Navaro Bowman did the drills.
So, it was good to see him do that, but
I couldn't give a final grade until I
saw him go through the movements that we
needed to see. You got a pretty good
feel when you watch the video and we
knew he could move and we knew he was
flexible and bandy and he liked contact
all the great things about Carson, but
you still need to confirm the All right,
cool. I see the power when he breaks or
whatever it is.
>> How hard is it like this year when
you're running those drills to balance
trying to watch and take in as many data
points as you can with your eyes and
your ears, but also remember that you
have to be running the drill.
>> Oh, I love that part. That's the best
part is like when they come up and it's
like, "All right, let's go Ohio State.
you got to do this better than the last
one or let's see who can do it the best
or you know at the end we we always
throw the wheel route where they catch
it then they come back and the last one
has to celebrate
>> you know so then I can tell they're
thinking about their celebration or
whatever but no it's a lot of fun it's a
lot of fun to get to know them and and
you just know when they you feel like
you know them pretty well when you're
down there and and you can feel the
power with which they move and and how
excited they are and and just who can
who can focus in the moment and roll.
So, no, I don't I think a few years ago
I might have gotten lost one time like,
"Oh, okay. I am up." But but it doesn't
happen that often.
>> When a guy like Sunny Styles does what
he did at the combine from just a
measurement and an overall standpoint,
is that something that around the
linebacker coach? I'm sure it's its own
little fraternity, right? The
linebackers, everybody like, "Oh my
goodness, did you guys see this? Did you
see that? Did you see what he jumped?
Did you see this?"
>> Yeah, he was great on the field. He was
really smart. Asked good questions.
Great lean body control. so fast and
just he's he's amazing guy. I mean, him
and him and our Ohio State guys, man,
>> there are a lot of those. Yeah, there
are a lot of them that are going to go
in the top 10 watch.
>> Yeah, I bet they were fun to watch. Do
you find that and this is obviously we
have a huge Ohio State audience
listening, but when you have guys that
come from a school where their DC was is
Matt Patricia, where a guy who's been a
head coach in the NFL, a DC in the NFL,
is that do they get a different kind of
preparation almost for what the NFL is
coming from a situation like that?
Because now if you look at them now they
have Arthur Smith as the OC now at Ohio
State. Patricia is the DC. I mean
>> yeah I worked with Ryan one year at the
Niners. I love Ryan and and uh I think I
got to sit with Matt for about 45
minutes because he came over to watch
watch the guys do the drills. So it was
great to talk to him talk to him about
the players but also just talk about
scheme and where he's gone and stuff.
And Matt's so smart and such a football
coach that it's amazing.
>> But I think all
>> overall from from evaluating linebackers
going on however many years it is. I
think that the the the uh the diagnose
and the uh development of linebackers
has just gotten better. There was a
there was an era where everybody went to
spread and it was just kind of spread
and now it's coming back to more where
where more tight ends and things and
it's happening at every level. And so I
think the the overall development of
linebackers and their eyes
>> is a little bit further ahead. And then
like you mentioned, the fact that either
coaches are moving or players are moving
more, they're more prepared for moving
and coming into the NFL than a younger
guy who maybe was a 20-year-old with
three years at one school,
>> one system.
>> Yeah. So that the more systems has
actually helped them learn quicker in
the football environments because
they've heard more words. Yeah. So I
think there's a lot of things going on
that way on the process. But I am we are
seeing more guys that their eyes are a
little bit trained earlier than than
maybe past years.
>> It's interesting.
>> Yeah, because they got they're learning
new systems all the time. So you
actually see how well they can process
and learn something.
>> They've done what they're about to do
>> before they've done it now where before
they hadn't. So the jump to the NFL
could be bigger for some guys. I mean
there's obviously guys like Carson and
some elite ones that just come in and
can just remember everything. But
>> is his story one of the crazier ones
you've been around? And you've been
around some great linebackers. But I'm
talking from the sense that this guy was
a noar
walk-on and really didn't play until his
last year because somebody got hurt at
the beginning of the year and then got a
chance. Like he might not have ever
played and then this guy was the best
rookie in the National Football League
one year later.
>> Yeah. The twoear span of what Carson's
done is amazing from you know the the
story the
>> but how how is he not on the field? How
is that guy how did everybody get that
wrong?
>> The everybody develops at a different
rate. One thing that happened with
Carson is
>> he's he's unique because he's got
>> he didn't get his weight until later.
He's got skills of a smaller human and
then he then he really developed when he
got there. Everybody everybody grows at
a different pace. You don't know when
that's going to happen. Some people are
given their gifts earlier and they're
just the top recruit in the nation the
whole time. Others Carson just went in
and worked just like he said here. I
want to earn it, coach. I just want to
earn it. He just went in and worked and
developed and and ate and trained and
grew. And then there was a point where
you could see it all take over. And it
really was in that Hawaii game when he
went in there was a blitz and and I've
told the story before and it broke and
he went and caught the guy and made just
like he does diving sweep the leg tackle
to save a touchdown. And then the last
drive where I got the ball back was
driving and Carson took the ball away
and that was when you kind of you could
just saw like not only does he is he
aware he plays with great effort and
look at this big guy running and hitting
and then it he just kept getting better
and better. So, I mean, but that span of
two years from that Hawaii game to the
end of last year, I don't know if that's
been done.
>> Certainly not with anybody that has his
quote unquote background. That's right.
This is what have you done for me lately
business is the sad reality of it. I
mean, it's true. It's true.
>> What's your one non-negotiable for a
linebacker in your room?
>> Okay. So, our mantra is, and you've
heard me say it, run, shed, tackle the
guy with the ball. Yeah. If you're not
running,
>> what are we doing? If the ball is up and
running until you tackle it, somebody
else does, or we take the thing away,
you run. So, what that word is, a lot of
people say loafs or whatever. Okay.
>> Those Uhuh. that the the effort is
non-negotiable.
>> Yep.
>> And then it's shed. Shed is next. So, we
you got to get off the blocks and make
plays, period. And they're going to hold
they're going to do everything they can
in this league. And these are big humans
grabbing you and they're really strong.
So, you got to get off the blocks. So,
our rule is shed is finish it down
unblocked. So, I'll you'll see it a lot
of times. You'll see our guys and look
for it. They'll be at the end of the
pile and they're just pushing things off
them or they're ripping. There's one
with Carson and the Miami center and
they're at the end of the play and
they're just pushing each other back and
forth and Carson just isn't even looking
at him, but he's like, "You are not
finishing the down touching me." And I
loved it and I started the meeting with
it. It's exactly what we do. And then
tackle the guy with the ball. We got to
get the guy on the ground and and get
the ball. I mean, separate him from the
ball. The running and the shedding is
are the non-negotiables and that's what
we do and that's what's going to
continue. If you earn the right to be on
the field, you'll be doing that. And if
you don't do that, somebody else is
coming on the field, right? So, that's
what that's what we care about in the
room and for our defense.
>> I love it. I think this is going to be
fun. I think that this defense is going
to be very fun and with your energy,
Rudy's energy, the the good staff. I'm
excited for it. I'm excited for it. When
do you get to get these guys and
actually get a look at them?
few weeks a couple weeks, right? Yeah.
And a few weeks here because we got the
new head coach. So So you get the the a
little bit extra starting time, which
would be good.
>> And uh we're excited to get everybody in
the building, new coaching staff,
everything. So
>> I imagine you're already needling win
and buie to get them be like, "This is
your chance." Eastn all these guys.
>> Yeah. Well, they're they're in doing
their doing their work and their rehab.
So So we they're they're grinding.
>> Oh, yeah. I see I see you give them a
little grief at lunch. I see it. I see
you getting them ready. Great. Jason
Tarver, linebacker, coach
extraordinaire. Always a pleasure when
you stop by, man. Thank you.
>> Thank you.